(Kurt:)Okay, maybe you didn't hear me.
(Kurt:)- Go away.
- All right, Kurt, be nice.
Oh, I am being nice.
Right, little buddy?
(Leonard:)- Kurt.
- Okay.
(Leonard:)I understand your impulse
to try to physically intimidate me.
(Leonard:)You can't compete with me
on an intellectual level...
(Leonard:)...and so you're driven
to animalistic puffery.
(Kurt:)You calling me a puffy animal?
Oh, of course not.
(Penny:)No, he's not. You're not, right, Leonard?
(Leonard:)No, I said animalistic.
(Leonard:)Of course, we're all animals...
(Leonard:)...but some of us have climbed
a little higher on the evolutionary tree.
(Sheldon:)If he understands that, you're in trouble.
So what? I'm unevolved?
(Sheldon:)You're in trouble.
(Kurt:)You know, you use a lot of big words
for such a little dwarf.
(Penny:)Okay, Kurt, please.
Look, Penny, it's okay.
(Leonard:)I can handle this.
I am not a dwarf, I'm a hobbit.
(Leonard:)A hobbit.
(Leonard:)Are misfiring neurons in your hippocampus
preventing the conversion...
(Leonard:)...from short-term to long-term memory?